jppss.k12.la.us 2010-04-06

# Jefferson Parish Public School System

Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit our websites, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit our websites, our web server automatically records information such as your IP address, network properties, browser capabilities, and geolocation. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved, and your personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to a newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the Jefferson Parish Public School System archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law. 

If you have other questions about this privacy policy, or have suggestions on how it may be improved, please feel free to [contact our webmaster](http://208.88.129.62/district/contactus/ContactUs.aspx "contact our webmaster") or call us directly at (504) 349-8968.
